Finding Aid for University Musical Society (University of Michigan) records, 1879-2009.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Director's Correspondence 1893-1983
  - 1981
    - Dispeker (Thea) Artists Representative
      - General (Box 105)
      - Ginestera/diBonaventura Performance (Box 105)
    - E (Box 105)
    - F (Box 105)
    - G (Box 105)
    - H (Box 105)
    - Hillyer (Kazuko) Management (Box 105)
    - I (Box 105)
    - ICM Artists Ltd. (Box 105)
    - J (Box 105)
    - K (Box 106)
    - L (Box 106)
    - M (Box 106)
    - N (Box 106)
    - O (Box 106)
    - P (Box 106)
    - Philadelphia Orchestra (Box 106)
    - R (Box 106)
    - S (Box 106)
    - Shaw Concerts Inc. (Box 106)
    - T (Box 106)
    - Thank You Notes (Box 106)
    - University of Michigan
      - Intra-University (Box 106)
      - Scheduling Office (Box 106)
      - School of Music (Box 106)
    - V (Box 106)
    - W (Box 106)
  - 1982
    - A (Box 106)
    - Ann Arbor Summer Festival (Box 106)
    - B (Box 106)
    - Barrett (Herbert) Management (Box 106)
    - Big Ten Concert Managers (Box 106)
    - C (Box 106)
    - Choral Union
      - General (Box 106)
      - Spanish Tour (Box 106)
    - Columbia Artists Management Inc. (Box 106)
    - Complaints (Box 106)
    - Contributors (Box 106)
    - D (Box 106)
    - Development (Box 106)
    - Dispeker (Thea) Artists Representative (Box 106)
    - E (Box 106)
    - F (Box 106)
    - Fan Letters (Box 106)
    - Festival Chorus (Box 106)
    - G (Box 106)
    - H (Box 106)
    - Hillyer (Kazuko) International Inc. (Box 106)
    - I (Box 106)
    - ICM Artists Ltd. (Box 106)
    - International Society of Performing Arts Administrators (ISPAA) (Box 106)
    - J (Box 106)
    - K (Box 106)
    - L (Box 106)
    - M (Box 106)
    - N (Box 106)
    - National Endowment for the Arts-Inter-Arts Program (Box 106)
    - O (Box 106)
    - P (Box 106)
    - Philadelphia Orchestra (Box 106)
    - R (Box 106)
    - Rector, Gail 25th Anniversary (responses to Dean Britton) (Box 106)
    - S (Box 106)
    - Shaw Concerts Inc. (Box 106)
    - Sonrise Video (Box 106)
    - T (Box 106)
    - University of Michigan
      - Intra-University (Box 106)
      - Scheduling Office (Box 106)
      - School of Music (Box 106)
    - V-Z (Box 106)
  - 1983
    - A (Box 106)
    - B (Box 106)
    - Barrett (Herbert) Management (Box 106)
    - Bregstein Film (Box 106)
    - C (Box 106)
    - Choral Union (Box 106)
    - Columbia Artists Management Inc. (Box 106)
    - Complaints (Box 106)
    - Contributors (Box 106)
    - D (Box 106)
    - Development (Box 106)
    - Dispeker (Thea) Artists Representative (Box 106)
    - E (Box 106)
    - F (Box 106)
    - G (Box 106)
    - H (Box 106)
    - I (Box 106)
    - ICM Artists Ltd. (Box 106)
    - International Society of Performing Arts Administrators (ISPAA) (Box 106)
    - J (Box 106)
    - K (Box 106)
    - L (Box 106)
    - M (Box 106)
    - May Festival (Box 106)
    - N (Box 106)
    - O (Box 106)
    - P (Box 106)
    - Philadelphia Orchestra (Box 106)
    - R (Box 106)
    - Rector, Gail 25th Anniversary (copies of testimonials) (Box 106)
    - S (Box 106)
    - Shaw Concerts Inc. (Box 106)
    - T (Box 106)
    - University of Michigan
      - Intra-University (Box 106)
      - Scheduling Office (Box 106)
      - School of Music (Box 106)
    - U,V (Box 106)
    - W (Box 106)
- Financial Records 1879-1940
  Financial Records consist of ledgers and account books dating form 1879 to 1940 and a file of material relating to the Frieze Memorial Organ Fund.
  - Ledgers and Account Books 1879-1940 (Box 65)
  - Ledgers and Account Books 1879-1940 (Box 66)
  - Ledgers and Account Books 1879-1940 (Box 67)
  - Material Concerning the Frieze Memorial Organ Fund (Box 67)
- Historical File, 1881-ca. 1980
  The series titled Historical File includes the original articles of association, bylaws and revisions through 1968; several histories of the UMS; records of the Choral Union and School of Music; and various reports.
  - Articles of Association/Bylaws, etc. 1881-1968 (Box 99)
  - Choral Union
    - Bonus 1907 (Extension of May Festival) (Box 99)
    - Record Books 1879-1891, 2 volumes (Box 99)
  - Clement, Lewis L. (scrapbook) (Box 99)
  - History of UMS (typescript), 2 folders (Box 99)
  - Histories of UMS (Gail Rector, Barbara Ferguson) (Box 99)
  - Kelsey, Francis W., Correspondence
    - Association of UMS with University 1904-1905 (Box 99)
    - Miscellaneous 1903-1916 (Box 99)
  - May Festival, First, 1894 (Box 99)
  - 100 Years of Great Performances, 1879-1979 (Box 99)
  - Music Teachers National Association circa 1885-1901 (Box 99)
  - Pond, Irving K. 1929-1936 (Box 99)
  - Personnel Records (including Music School) K-Z 1889-1938 (Box 99)
  - Printed (Box 99)
  - Reports
    - General 1882 (Box 99)
    - Director and Other Reports 1924-1938 (Box 99)
      (1926 1929, 1930 missing)
    - Financial (Box 99)
    - 1881-1912 (1884-1889 missing) (Box 99)
    - 1913-1921 (1920 missing) (Box 100)
    - 1921-1939 (Box 100)
    - State of Michigan 1915-1939 (Box 100)
  - "The Role of the UMS...," 1968 (Box 100)
  - School of Music
    - Building Association, Articles of Association 1893 (Box 100)
    - Faculty information 1939-1940 (Box 100)
    - Minutes and miscellaneous 1939-1940 (Box 100)
  - University Musical Society
    - Minutes 1881-1938, 2 volumes (Box 100)
    - Miscellaneous unbound items found in minute books (Box 100)
  - White, Andrew 1904-1906 (Box 100)
  - International Association of Concert and Festival Managers 1969-1972 (Box 100)
- Board of Directors 1938-2001
  The Board of Directors series is divided into four subseries: Miscellaneous Files, 1876-1983; Minutes/Financial Reports, 1938-1994; Meeting Packets, 1988-2001; and Audiotapes, 1954-1988. The Miscellaneous subseries contains several folders of primarily correspondence dating from 1976 to 1983.
  The minutes were bound and the pages consecutively numbered through June 1989. This series includes thirteen bound volumes (1876 through June 1989) and loose minutes (July 1989 through July 1994). Both the bound and the loose minutes include related items documenting the activities of the Board of Directors, its Executive Committee and the following UMS committees: Development, Long-Range Planning/Implementation, Budget and Finance and Marketing. Minutes of the annual meeting of the University Musical Society are included in the Board of Directors Minutes. Earlier minutes of the UMS are found in earlier accessions. Please consult the summary contents lists for information about the complete run of minutes.
  The Board of Directors Packets were maintained by UMS staff for February and April 1988 and for the years 1990 through June 1997. Included in the packets are agendas and minutes (which may duplicate materials in the previous series) and additional background information prepared for the board members, including reports from standing committees such as Development, Marketing, Programming, and Long-Range Planning.
  The audiotapes of Board of Directors meetings (99 cassettes) span 1954-1988, but do not provide a complete run of the meetings.
  - Miscellaneous
    - 1976-1983, 8 folders (Box 102)
    - Heydon, Peter 1980-1982 (Box 102)
  - Minutes/Financial Reports (bound volumes)
    - 1938-1946 (Box 102)
    - 1947-1956 (Box 102)
    - 1957-1963 (Box 102)
    - May 1964-November 1968 (Box 112)
    - January 1969-May 1972 (Box 112)
    - September 1972-September 1974 (Box 112)
    - December 1974-April 1977 (Box 112)
    - July 1977-April 1979 (Box 112)
    - July 1979-September 1981 (Box 113)
    - December 1981-September 1983 (Box 113)
    - December 1983-December 1985 (Box 113)
    - February 1986-February 1988 (Box 113)
    - April 1988-June 1989 (Box 113)
    - July 1989-June 1990 (Box 113)
    - September 1990-June 1991 (Box 113)
    - September 1991-July 1992 (Box 113)
    - September 1992-December 1992 (Box 113)
    - January 1993-June 1993 (Box 114)
    - July 1993-September 1993 (Box 114)
    - October 1993-January 1994 (Box 114)
    - February 1994-June 1994 (Box 114)
    - July 1994 (Box 114)
  - Meeting Packets 1988-2005
    - February April 1988 (Box 114)
    - 1990 (Box 114)
    - 1991 (Box 114)
    - 1992 (Box 114)
    - 1994-1995, 3 folders (Box 114)
    - 1995-1996, 5 folders (Box 114)
    - September 1996-June 1997, 8 folders (Box 115)
    - September 1997-June 1998, 6 folders (Box 121)
      [ER RESTRICTED until July 1, 2030 ]
    - September 1998-June 1999, 6 folders (Box 121)
    - September 1999-June 2000, 6 folders (Box 121)
    - September 2000-June 2001, 5 folders (Box 121)
    - September 2002-June 2003, 4 folders (Box 128)
    - September 2003-June 2004, 2 folders (Box 128)
    - September 2004-June 2005, 4 folders (Box 128)
  - Audio Recordings of Board of Directors Meetings
    - 1954-1988, 99 audiocassettes (Box 111)
- Committees 1975-1995
  The Committees series consists primarily of Advisory Committee and one folder and an outsize bound volume of financial records. The Advisory Committee folders include minutes and related correspondence. The minutes tend to be scattered and do not provide a complete run of Advisory Committee meetings. There is also one folder of material on the Finance Committee
  - Advisory Committee 1975-1995
    - Minutes and Correspondence 1975-1995
      - 1975-1983, 9 folders (Box 102)
      - January-May 1984 1984/85-1994/95, 9 folders (Box 112)
    - Rosters, 1974- 1994/95 Event Reports, 1986-1988 (Box 112)
  - Finance Committee 1975-1976 (Box 102)
- Topical Files
  A wide array of subjects is covered in the Topical Files series. Records and correspondence that document the inception of the first Ann Arbor Summer Festival are included, as are similar materials for the Fair Lane Festival, a summer endeavor of the University Musical Society that took place in 1967, on the grounds of the Henry Ford estate on the University of Michigan-Dearborn campus. Of additional interest is a folder that lists the world premieres presented by the UMS and two folders of historical materials which include a letter and prints of Jenny Lind, the legendary Swedish singer of the late nineteenth century. Additional material includes a musical autograph of violinist and composer Fritz Kreisler.
  - Ann Arbor Summer Festival
    - Art Exhibit 1984 (Box 102)
    - Board of Trustees (Box 102)
    - 1980-81 (Box 102)
    - 1984 (Box 102)
    - Clippings 1984 (Box 102)
    - Correspondence (Box 102)
    - 1983 (Box 102)
    - 1984 (Box 102)
    - Development 1984 (Box 102)
    - Financial Information 1984 (Box 102)
    - Food Service 1984 (Box 102)
    - Minutes, Reports 1984 (Box 102)
    - Promotional/Marketing 1984 (Box 102)
    - Women's Committee (Gala) 1984 (Box 102)
  - Auditorium Agreements 1976/77-1983/84, 8 folders (Box 102)
  - Bank Book 1933-1945 (Box 103)
  - Choral Union
    - Brochure 1979 (Box 103)
    - Repertoire List (Box 103)
  - Clippings 1971-1983 (Box 103)
  - Commissions
    - 1977-1980 (Box 103)
    - Menotti, Gian Carlo 1977-1980 (Box 103)
  - Copyright Law 1977-1979 (Box 103)
  - Dance Residencies, 1975/76- 1981-1982, 7 folders (Box 103)
  - Fair Lane Festival 1967
    - Clippings (Box 103)
    - Memos, Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 103)
    - Programs (Box 103)
    - Reports (Box 103)
    - Stage and Canopy Plans (Box 103)
  - Francescatti, Zino Interview 1961 (Box 103)
  - Hill Auditorium 1975-1978 (Box 103)
  - Historical Materials
    - Autographs (Box 103)
    - Lind, Jenny (Box 103)
  - Historical Survey (Box 103)
  - Johnson, Thor
    - Clippings (Box 103)
    - Programs, Memorials (Box 103)
  - News Releases 1977-1984 (Box 103)
  - Office Policies 1980 (Box 103)
  - 100th Anniversary Citations (Box 103)
  - Premieres (World and U.S.) (Box 103)
  - Sink, Charles A. (Box 103)
- Contracts 1933-2001
  The Contracts series provides copies of the final contracts for performances for the years 1933/34-1984/85 and 1986-2001. The earlier seasons tend to be represented more completely than the later. Contracts for seasons in the 1970s and 1980s are not represented in their entirety. For the most part, these files include only contracts, no accompanying correspondence. Cover letters and related correspondence are found in the Correspondence series. The 1986-2001 contracts are closed.
  - 1933/34-1968/69, 37 folders (Box 107)
  - 1971/72-1977/78, 7 folders (Box 108)
  - 1979/80 (Box 108)
  - 1983/84 (Box 108)
  - 1984/85 (Box 108)
  - Ann Arbor Summer Festival 1985 (Box 108)
  - 1986/87-2004/05
    [Closed for Research, Records Center Storage]
    - 1986/87-2004/05 (Box 124)
    - 1986/87-2004/05 (Box 125)
      (continued)
    - 1986/87-2004/05 (Box 126)
    - 1986/87-2004/05 (Box 127)
- Photographs
  The Photographs series is organized into four subseries: Facilities, Portraits, Artist and Performance Photos, and Unidentified and Miscellaneous. The Facilities file contains pictures of Hill Auditorium. The Portraits subseries consist of pictures of members of the UMS Board of Directors and UMS officers.
  Artist and Performance Photographs include several oversized mounted prints of performances from May Festivals in 1918, 1943 and 1946. The bulk of the series consists of, with very rare exceptions, a complete run of artist photographs for concerts from the 1957/58 season through 1977/78. These photographs were maintained by the UMS along with the corresponding programs. In the 1968/69 and subsequent folders, reviews of concerts are also included. The majority of the photographs came from the artists themselves, and most of them are also autographed. The boxlist includes a note of those photographs for each year that were taken locally, many of them at Hill Auditorium. In locating a photograph of a given artist, it may serve the researcher well to first look through the programs included in the UMS Publications, and then locate the corresponding folder of photographs.
  - Facilities
    - Hill Auditorium (Box 101)
  - Portraits, 4 folders
    - Albert A. Stanley, Choral Union Conductor, 1888-1921 (Box 101)
    - Sarah Power, Board of Directors, 1972-1986 (Box 101)
    - Lois Stegeman, Board of Directors, 1975-1987 (Box 101)
    - Thor Johnson, Conductor, 1939-1942; Board, 1941-1968 (Box 101)
    - Jerry Weisbach, Board of Directors, 1983-1988 (Box 101)
    - Richard Kennedy, Board of Directors, 1985- (Box 101)
    - Paul Kauper, Board of Directors, 1968-1974 (Box 101)
    - Alexander Winchell, President, 1881-1883, 1889-1891 (Box 101)
    - Douglas Crary, Board of Directors, 1968-1987 (Box 101)
    - E. Thurston Thieme, Board of Directors, 1963-1986 (Box 101)
    - Harry Burns Hutchins, Board of Directors, 1899-1930 (Box 101)
    - Thomas Read, Lieutenant Governor of Michigan (Box 101)
    - Horace G. Prettyman, Board of Directors, 1916-1945 (Box 101)
    - Calvin B. Cady, Conductor, 1879-1888; Board, 1881-1888 (Box 101)
    - Oscar A. Eberbach, Board of Directors, 1926-1968 (Box 101)
    - Durand W. Springer, Board of Directors, 1904-1943 (Box 101)
    - Victor C. Vaughan, Board of Directors, 1899-1923 (Box 101)
    - William C. Stevens, Board of Directors, 1894-1921 (Box 101)
    - Shirley W. Smith, Board of Directors, 1910-1959 (Box 101)
    - Harley A. Haynes, Board of Directors, 1927-1965 (Box 101)
    - Roscoe O. Bonisteel, Board of Directors, 1938-1972 (Box 101)
    - Clarence C. Little, Board of Directors, 1926-1930 (Box 101)
    - James Ingliss, Board of Directors, 1921-1950 (Box 101)
    - Levi D. Wines, Board of Directors, 1884-1938 (Box 101)
    - John Paul, Board of Directors, 1983- (Box 101)
    - Harold Shapiro, Board of Directors, 1979-1987 (Box 101)
    - Paul R. B. de Pont, Board of Directors, 1881-1906 (Box 101)
    - Howard S. Holmes, 1984-1987 (Box 101)
    - Harlan Hatcher, Board of Directors, 1951-1982 (Box 101)
    - Merlin Wiley, Board of Directors, 1942-1963 (Box 101)
    - E. Blythe Stason, Board of Directors, 1939-1968 (Box 101)
    - Ottmar Eberbach, Board of Directors, 1892-1921 (Box 101)
    - Albert E. Sleeper, Governor of Michigan (Box 101)
    - Charles H. Ditson, Donor of Oliver Ditson Endowment, 1845-1929 (Box 101)
    - Harvey J. Howard, Personal Friend of Charles Sink (?) (Box 101)
    - Henry Stewart Dean, Board of Directors, 1882-1915 (Box 101)
    - G. Frank Almendinger, Board of Directors, 1891-1927 (Box 101)
    - Gail Rector, UMS President, 1968-1987 (Box 101)
    - James H. Wade, Board of Directors, 1892-1925 (Box 101)
    - Henry F. Vaughan, Board of Directors, 1942-1968 (Box 101)
  - Artist and Performance Photos
    (located at Bimul N1)
    - May Festival May 18-21, 1918, 21 photographs mounted on 22" x35" board (Folder Bimul N1)
    - Golden Jubilee May Festival with the Philadelphia Orchestra and Eugene Ormandy May 5-8, 1943, mounted on 13" x 21" board (Folder Bimul N1)
    - 1946 May Festival with the Philadelphia Orchestra and Eugene Ormandy, mounted on 12" x 21" board (Folder Bimul N1)
    - 1946 May Festival Youth Chorus, Philadelphia Orchestra, and Marguerite Hood (conductor), mounted on 10" x 21" board (Folder Bimul N1)
    - Fairlane Festival 1967, 4 prints 11" x 14" 35mm negatives (Box 101)
    - 1957/58 (Box 108)
      (includes Boston Symphony)
    - 1958/59 (Box 108)
      (includes Renata Tibaldi and Gail Rector)
    - May Festival 1959 (Box 108)
      (includes Eugene Ormandy, Gail Rector and Dorothy Kirsten, Philadelphia Orchestra rehearsal, Robert Courte)
    - 1959/60 (Box 108)
    - May Festival 1960 (Box 108)
    - 1960/61 (Box 108)
      (includes Van Cliburn, Jerome Hines, Warsaw Philharmonic, Yehudi Menuhin, Rudolf Serkin)
    - May Festival 1961 (Box 108)
      (includes May Festival Soloists)
    - 1961/62 (Box 108)
    - May Festival 1962 (Box 108)
    - 1962/63 (Box 108)
      (includes Birgit Nilsson and Gail Rector)
    - May Festival 1963 (Box 108)
    - 1963/64 (Box 108)
      (includes New York Philharmonic, Chicago Opera Ballet, Anna Moffo and Gail Rector)
    - May Festival 1964 (Box 108)
      (includes Phillipe Entremont)
    - 1964/65 (Box 108)
      (includes Andres Segovia)
    - May Festival 1965 (Box 108)
      (includes Philadelphia Orchestra rehearsals)
    - 1965/66 (Box 108)
    - May Festival 1966 (Box 108)
    - 1966/67 includes Andres Segovia and Gail Rector, Artur Rubenstein (Box 109)
    - May Festival 1967 (Box 109)
    - 1967/68 includes Roger Sessions and Jean Martinon (Box 109)
    - May Festival 1968 (Box 109)
    - 1968/69 (Box 109)
      (includes Moscow State Symphony)
    - May Festival 1969 (Box 109)
    - Summer Series 1969 (Box 109)
    - 1969/70 (Box 109)
      (includes new kiosk at Hill Auditorium)
    - May Festival 1970 (Box 109)
    - 1970/71 (Box 109)
      (includes Jean Martinon and Orchestre French Radio and Television)
    - May Festival 1971 includes Leontyne Price, Eugene Ormandy and Gail Rector (Box 109)
    - 1971/72, 2 folders (Box 109)
      (includes Messiah, Andres Segovia, and Alicia de Larrocha and Gail Rector)
    - May Festival 1972 (Box 109)
    - 1972/73, 2 folders (Box 109)
      (includes UM VP Richard Kennedy and Gail Rector)
    - May Festival 1973 (Box 109)
    - 1973/74, 2 folders (Box 109)
      (includes Bela Bartok, Jr., Gyorgy Sandor and Gail Rector, Leningrad Philharmonic and Choral Union)
    - May Festival 1974 (Box 109)
    - 1974/75, 2 folders (Box 110)
      (includes Msitislav Rostropovich and University Symphony, Seigi Ozawa and Donald Bryant(?))
    - May Festival 1975 (Box 110)
    - 1975/76, includes Yehudi Menuhin, 2 folders (Box 110)
    - May Festival 1976 (Box 110)
    - 1976/77 (Box 110)
    - May Festival 1977 (Box 110)
    - 1977/78, 2 folders (Box 110)
      (includes Robert Shaw, Vladimir Horowitz)
    - May Festival 1978 (Box 110)
    - Baltimore Symphony 1980 (local photos) (Box 110)
    - Choral Union 1893-1974 (Box 110)
    - Egyptian Tour 1978 (Box 110)
    - Fair Lane Festival 1967
      (See Also Box 101)
      - Caramoor Festival Ensemble (Box 110)
      - Concert Goers (Box 110)
      - Grounds (Box 110)
      - Iturbi, Jose and Shumsky, Oscar (Box 110)
      - Martinon, Jean (Box 110)
      - Menuhin, Yehudi (Box 110)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 110)
      - Orchestra (Chicago Symphony) (Box 110)
      - Soloists (Box 110)
    - Johnson, Thor (Box 110)
    - Museum of Art/Summer Festival Exhibit 1984 (Box 110)
    - Sink, Charles A. (Box 110)
    - UMS Group May 19, 1986 (Box 110)
  - Unidentified and Miscellaneous Photographs
    - Orchestra and Chorus undated, mounted on 18" x 30" board (Folder Bimul N1)
    - Orchestra and Chorus undated, mounted on 18" x 26" board (Folder Bimul N1)
    - Residence of Alexander Winchell which occupied the site where Hill Auditorium now stands, 12" x 21" (Folder Bimul N1)
      (Rentschler copy)
    - Fiddle Sketch of Eugene Ormandy by Nathan Milstein, May 3, 10" x 13" (Folder Bimul N1)
- President's and Executive Director's Correspondence 1928, 1930-1935, 1984-1988
  The President's and Executive Director's Correspondence series includes one folder of correspondence created by UMS President Charles Sink regarding the May Festival, 1928 and 1930-1935. The correspondence of President Gail Rector covers the years 1984 through July 1987 when Rector retired as president of the University Musical Society. The correspondence of Executive Director Kenneth Fischer begins in 1987 and continues through 1988. The correspondence is organized alphabetically; the 1988 files include two folders of correspondence organized in chronological order.
  The correspondence documents communication with artists' agents, artists, concert goers and other arts managers. Included is documentation of the Ann Arbor Summer Festival (AASF) with which Gail Rector was active. Ann Arbor Summer Festival Board of Trustees minutes, and files related to the AASF Executive Committee, Programming Committee and Marketing Committee were not kept as they can be found in the papers of Eugene Power also held by the Bentley Library. Eugene Power founded the festival in 1978.
  For the first few years of Kenneth Fischer's tenure as executive director, the UMS staff used the same alphabetical filing system for correspondence. With Fischer's tenure, a topical file, not broken by year, was also instituted (see Topical Files below).
  - President Charles Sink
    - May Festival 1928, 1930-1935 (Box 115)
  - President Gail W. Rector
    - 1984
      - A (Box 115)
      - Ann Arbor Summer Festival 1984, 2 folders (Box 115)
      - B (Box 115)
      - Big Ten Concert Managers (Box 115)
      - Board of Directors (Box 115)
      - C (Box 115)
      - Columbia Artists Management Inc. (Box 115)
      - Complaints (Box 115)
      - Contributors (Box 115)
      - D (Box 115)
      - Development (Box 115)
      - E, F (Box 115)
      - G (Box 115)
      - H (Box 115)
      - I (Box 115)
      - Inquiries from artists and managers (Box 115)
      - Intra-university (Box 115)
      - J, K (Box 115)
      - L (Box 115)
      - M (Box 115)
        (includes May Festival and Messiah)
      - N (Box 115)
        (includes grant application to NEA)
      - O, P (Box 115)
      - R (Box 115)
      - S (Box 115)
      - T, U, V (Box 115)
      - W, XYZ (Box 115)
    - 1985 (Box 116)
      - A (Box 116)
      - Ann Arbor Summer Festival 1985 (Box 116)
      - B (Box 116)
      - Big Ten Concert Managers (Box 116)
      - Board of Directors (Box 116)
      - C (Box 116)
      - Columbia Artists Management, Inc. (Box 116)
      - D (Box 116)
      - E, F (Box 116)
      - Flint 1985-1986 Spotlight Series (Box 116)
      - G (Box 116)
      - H (Box 116)
      - I (Box 116)
      - Inquiries from artists and managers (Box 116)
      - Intra-university (Box 116)
      - J, K (Box 116)
      - L (Box 116)
      - M (Box 116)
      - N (Box 116)
      - O, P (Box 116)
      - R, S (Box 116)
      - T, U, V (Box 116)